It's my life.
It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Any one more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a winter fire.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going.
I'll not stay.
Let's do it again.
You know what I mean, baby!
No one can make my dream come true?
Don't you feel it?
I really don't know what is
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away the great
end of the unknown rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you only without.
It's my life, it's your life.
Party for tomorrow, go
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your eyes that
I want, but your weary ones.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life,
shine like a star to be good.
I know you're strong, just that
you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going out of day.
You make my day every day.
Show that tramp the door.
Hey, hey, Law.
It's been about a week, bud.
Bet you're here to call it quits, huh?
I can't really blame you.
You've been Corazon's personal
bungee bag since you got here.
I'm shocked a runt like
you stuck it out so long.
When things get tough, we
usually see the weaklings bail.
You gotta have some big stones
if you want to run with us.
We have a blood law around here.
If executives aren't shown proper respect,
the family falls apart This
one time, I cracked up at Mr.
Pika's voice and then
nearly tortured me to death
If you're trying to scare
me off, it won't work.
I've already experienced true hell.
You play a good hand, kid,
but I see through your bluff.
Regardless, Corazon is
my dear brother by blood.
Should I find out anyone
lays a scratch on him?
Let's just say it's curtains for them.
Keep away from us boy.
That's white lead disease
Stop Jola you should know
better than to spout nonsense
as facts shame on you look
at that you wound Buffalo up
It's caused by a toxin that
can't spread person to person.
Just stay away!
I don't care how you get it!
I'm not catching your gross-ass cuties!
Tell me, are you the last one left, or are
there any other survivors of White Town?
Hell if I know.
I was busy escaping!
And how did you manage to get away?
I hid an amount of dead bodies,
then snuck over the border.
Come on, we're eating!
I bet you have an axe to grind.
These days I don't believe in anything
and I'm not even afraid to die,
so don't go pressing your
luck with me, Corazon.
I have nothing to lose and before my
time comes, I plan on taking you down.
Are you that dumb?
Weren't you listening?
We're not above torturing
kids here, so don't try it!
You should never mess with
pirates and crying won't
save you because we're
living in a grown-up's world,
okay?
Hey, so what's the deal with
that white town thing anyway?
It's another name for
the kingdom of Flevins.
What do you want to know about it?
What was it like?
It was a wealthy place and everything
from their soil to their foliage was
pure white Visiting was like stepping
into a snow-filled fairytale kingdom.
It was often described as
having an unusual beauty to it.
One day, they unearthed a type
of metal called white lead.
Just beneath their kingdom's surface,
it was discovered that this was the
source of their breathtaking landscape.
They harvested this metal and
used it to make tableware,
paints, sweeteners,
cosmetics, and even weapons.
These unique products drew attention from
all over the world and
became high in demand.
This, in turn, made
Flevince's economy boom.
Even the world government took notice and
profited by helping to export their goods.
White lead was a cash grab
for all those involved.
Law, for this kind of surgery, you
should focus on these blood vessels.
I get it.
Hey, brother, you want
to go to the festival?
What if you two took him?
I can't fight that. Sound like fun?
Just 30 minutes, though.
I still have a fair number
of patients to see today.
Oh, yeah!
Law, please say you'll go.
For your family.
Huh?
At one point in time, Whitetown was
the fascination of the entire world.
I want to go there, too!
Regrettably, it's gone!
With a capital G.
Huh?
A century ago, when the white
lead industry first began,
the world government surveyed
the land scrutinously.
The truth is, Flevance held a secret.
What's the secret?
White lead's toxic.
If left intact underground, it
posed little harm, but once handled,
it slowly poisoned its victims.
Sadly,
both the government and the royalty
were so blinded by the incredible wealth
they were accumulating that they brushed
the dangerous truth under the rug.
The citizens continued to excavate the
white lead without knowing the risks.
So that means all those
poor people must have died?
That's right.
Appallingly, the suffering of
Flevitz's population doesn't end there.
Let's say a young man has even a
trace amount of lead in his body.
If he eventually has offspring,
that child's life expectancy would
already be shortened at birth.
And when that child grew into an
adult and had children of their own,
their lifespan would
be even shorter still.
The life expectancy kept reducing until
eventually it reached law's generation.
They died before making it to
adulthood unfortunately by the time the
world caught on that white lead was
dangerous it was already too late.
Slowly their population started
to collapse one after another.
Grandparents mothers fathers
children the shifting life
expectancies caused the
generations to fall ill around
the same time they all showed
similar symptoms their skin
and hair turned white as
their bodies writhed in pain.
No doctor could stop their suffering
so
that
means
every single person from
his kingdom died out there.
So smart but then the
real misfortune began.
Thing is neighboring
countries watched this
unfold and with white
towns population dropping
like flies they made an
assumption that white
lead disease was a highly
contagious disorder.
They cut them off in
all directions isolating
them while ignorantly turning a blind eye
with the help from the world government
their royals all safely fled the country.
Leaving their citizens behind.
And when people from Whitetown
tried to escape that hellhole,
be it in search of treatment
or their own safety,
they were treated like monsters
breaking out of their cages.
Shot on sight.
Without hesitation.
Just one more injustice covered
up by those in power. Damn it!
They convinced themselves that
it's their problem, not ours.
Guess that's humanity for you, huh?
But flevins didn't go
down without a fight.
They had an abundance of lead
on hand, including bullets.
Naturally, war broke out.
This gave surrounding countries
the justification to strike back,
and they did so without mercy.
I'm sure you can imagine
how that wrapped up.
There you are.
La, you must come with us.
We encountered some
compassionate soldiers.
They agreed to let you children escape.
La, let's go!
We gotta get out of here.
I can't.
Not while my little sister is dying.
I need to be there for her. Lammy's dying.
I'm sorry.
In that case, I'll ask them to save
you a spot on the next ship then.
I vow to come back for you. Law!
You're not coming too!
Now's our chance!
Run away with us!
We'll come back for Lammy later!
My dad both died already!
They told me to do
whatever I can to live on!
That's why I'm gonna live no matter what!
It's okay. Don't forget.
Even in darkness, there's hope.
Law, don't cry.
I, when times are at their gloomiest,
just know someone's watching over you.
Doctor!
Please help!
I need a doctor!
That's impossible.
I can't make it there.
Please, we're short-staffed.
Plus, we're in dire
need of blood donations.
There must be a way to remove the
white lead from a contaminated body.
It's not contagious either!
Why won't the government address that yet?
I can't move, Law.
My body hurts everywhere, and
my skin keeps getting blotchier.
Keep hanging in there, Lammy.
Our father is the best
doctor in the whole kingdom.
I know he'll fix you up.
Why is it so noisy outside
right now? Another festival.
Flevents has always been the kind
of town that likes to show off.
Anyway, get well soon so we can
go to the next one together.
Let me hide in here until I come get you.
Located at Purse 2.
Oh!
Ma.
Ma, please say you'll go.
For your family.
Wake up, Mom!
No!
It's okay.
Don't forget, even in
darkness, there's hope.
When times are at their gloomiest,
Just know someone's watching over you.
Sister!
Everybody!
You're not coming too!
That's why I'm gonna live no matter what!
The hospital!
Abby!
And just like that, the beautiful
white down Flavens was destroyed.
In the end, greed always comes out on top.
If I went through that at 10, I'd
be screwed up in the head, too.
You can't blame the kid for
being rough around the edges.
There, that's Corazon.
It's not fair that my parents,
my sister, and my friends from the church
died when this idiot is allowed to live.
I'll do this quietly and go unnoticed.
Nobody will care.
If one scumbag goes missing!
Jim, he saw me!
Oh no!
You're in so much trouble!
You broke the blood law and
now you're gonna get impaled!
I'm telling on you!
Young Master!
They're a family of Celestial Dragons!
Let's hang them!
They're former Celestial Dragons.
The Navy won't care if we kill them.
They'll just look the other way.
We'll finally have a chance
to retaliate against them.
I never thought I'd see the day.
Let's break their bones with a hammer!
Shower them with arrows!
Wait!
Don't kill them yet!
We need to keep them alive,
so they can really suffer!
Listen, bastards!
You took my two cents from me!
They were innocent children!
They just walked in front of a
celestial dragon, that's all!
But they paid the ultimate price!
How is that even fair?
My daughter was their slave!
She barely escaped her captors alive!
She came home, devastated, and
killed herself three days later!
I, too, suffered as a slave.
My eyes, because of you, I am blind.
I'll never get to see my wife again.
You, you treated us like animals.
So why should we give a damn, huh?
Because of the heavenly
tribute, we must forfeit to you.
Our beautiful nations succumb to famine.
Have you ever been hungry
a day in your life?
Our people are dying from starvation.
You're all like gods, aren't you?
If that's true, you won't die.
So I can shoot you all I want.
Duffy.
You monsters.
We're human.
But you treat us like we're
nothing more than insects.
Have you ever known grief?
Even once in your life,
have you fell agony?
Well, we're gonna show it to you.
No, no, no, no,
no!
What is it?
Law did what?
Have you gone mad, Saint Homing?
Surely you haven't thought this through!
Why would a man in your position reject
your divine right to live as a human?
But we are human, are we not?
Don't include us in that
ludicrous statement, you fool!
Take that right back!
That accusation's blasphemy!
You filthy traitor!
We've always known you
to be a raving heretic!
He's right!
You're a traitor!
Have you lost your mind?
How obscene!
Leave Marie Joie at once!
This is as far as we're
permitted to take you.
We're in the northern
end of our parameters and
approaching a region unaffiliated
with the world government.
Your living quarters and belongings
have been prepared for you.
Thank you.
This should be more than adequate.
Now, please hand over your
Celestial Dragon ID chips.
Well, this is it. We'll live humbly.
This should be fun, right?
Where are the slaves, Daddy?
If they ran away, we
should buy some new ones.
Dolfi, Rosanante, things will be
different from now on. I must teach you
I'm gonna need you to calm down.
We're humans from this day forward
Humans? Uh-huh. From now on,
we shall leave our old
lives back in Marajoie
A simpler life will be
much more fulfilling.
True wealth lies here.
Fools, listen, you must kneel.
Show me.
Respect, someone go fetch me my gun.
Who do you think I am?
You buffoon shouldn't mess with me.
Where are the celestial dragons?
Find them.
Let's hang them.
Daddy, why are they
not kneeling before me?
They're not here, they must have fled.
Find them!
They can't have gone too far!
Make it a slow death!
We want them to suffer!
Yeah!
We're gonna take out centuries
of revenge on that family!
Yeah!
Daddy!
Daddy, why?
Everyone is coming after us!
On the bright side, at
least the rain let up,
and we seem to have lost track
of the angry mob chasing us.
How can you expect us to
live in this filthy box?
There are bugs everywhere, and this
rotten stench is gonna make me hurl!
They must still be
nearby—find that family!
They're gonna die.
die
We should leave, quickly.
I could never have predicted
this would turn out so poorly.
I was far too optimistic.
So please, just take us back.
Even just my wife and children.
They deserve to return at the very least.
I fear if we stay here any
longer, we'll be slain.
What has been abandoned
cannot be returned.
You chose this life for yourself.
And don't you dare call us again,
you worthless human filth. Kalik.
Damn. Bread thieves!
Daddy, for the first time
in my life, I feel pain.
in my life, I'm hungry.
Eat up quick, Rosie.
The first time I've come.
Mommy, we brought you some food.
Sophie, Rosie.
You okay?
I'm sorry, boys.
I feel unwell.
Daddy...
Mother...
is dead.
We found him!
Not my boys! But Mercy!
The children! Let them go!
Please! Please!
Daddy!
You bastard!
You did this to us!
Young master, we have apprehended law.
It seems like the boy was
trying to make a run for it.
Jimmy, let me go!
At the port, tried fleeing.
What kind of punishment do you
think they'll use at him, huh?
To know.
Sure feel bad for him, though.
Corazon!
Damn!
I didn't take him out!
Now they're gonna kill me for nothing.
I thought bribing buffalo with
ice cream would cover it up.
But that scumbag Cora ratted me out!
I could've sworn I stabbed
him right through his body.
But he's acting like nothing happened!
Law.
I called you to discuss something.
Can you guess?
I wanted to welcome you to the
Don Quixote family officially.
Congrats, kid.
Welcome home, la!
Just looking at you, I can tell
you've been through hell and back.
You have that hate-filled
glare in your eyes.
I think you'll have a
lot to offer our family.
You hear that? Lovely!
Young master is a brilliant
judge of character.
Does he not know about
me stabbing Corazon yet?
Why not?
He could have just written it
out on a piece of paper for him.
What exactly is he planning?
Yeah, whatever.
I got three years.
And then I'm gonna die. The end. Done.
Maybe.
Depends on your luck. Luck?
Allow me to explain.
We're what you call experts
in the black market,
and one of our fields is devil fruits.
Their powers are vast, sometimes
beyond human comprehension.
Meaning there may be a Devil Fruit
that could cure your condition.
Devil fruits, huh?
So what?
You have three years left.
Who knows how many devil
fruits we'll find in that time.
And one of them just might have
a life-altering solution for you.
But for the time being,
I'd like to train you to be my
right-hand man ten years from now.
What happened?
Stabbed by an enemy.
You take care of him?
Very good, then.
Now patch that up.
Did Karoo just cover for me?
Why?
What's going on in his head?
We'll head toward Reverse
Mountain in the south.
I'd like to keep moving our base,
expand our network on the way.
Let's go.
That's right.
Come on, we told our real names. So what?
It's not like I asked.
Aw, lame.
You meanie.
Why does it matter?
I'll be dead soon enough.
Maybe. You're paler. You feel sick?
I'm fine for now, I guess.
But before too long, I'll be gone.
In that case, it's one more
reason to reveal your real name.
Just say it, or I'll tell
everyone that you stabbed Karoo!
It's Trafalgar.
Dee, Water Law.
Tell no one.
I'm actually not supposed to
let people hear my full name.
So just stick to law.
I don't use code names like you.
I just hide some parts.
Like Dee, that secret.
My true name is Water.
For generations, my
family - Okay, we get it.
This is boring.
We don't care.
I only told you because
you were harassing me.
What are you doing?
What's the big deal, Corazon?
Let go of me.
He's gonna get beat up again.
Cora looks scarier than usual.
Uh-oh.
What's your problem, stupid jerk?
What you just said, was it true?
Who said that?
Your secret name's D.
If that's right, you need
to get the hell out of here.
Away from Dofi.
Law, listen.
You cannot be around him.
You have to get out of here.